Peter
are you hiding
something?
How dare you?
I've never
so insulted
in my life Tom
Tom
Peter
is not British
He's from
New York
ohh
he is
oh
give me a minute
let me
okay
Peter
are you
hiding something?
oh
Why won't you just
give it a rest?
mate
will ya
You’re
tearing me
apart
Maybe a little
less dramatic
yea
I can
I
yeah
I can try funny
Peter
are you
hiding something?
*chockes on the water*
Me?
Please
let's take
a break
Do you want to
see some more?
I have loads more
Sure
Peter
are you
hiding something?
Yeah
Those my
delicious
burrito
I can't understand
you Tom
you can’t
understand
what I am saying?
I said
These are
so delicious
Tom
Let’s do one
without the
chips
Peter
are you
hiding something?
hey
Spider-Man
doesn't do that
Can we
try something
else?
Peter
are you
hiding something?
*dances in*
*starts jumnping*
No
The musical
closed a couple
years ago